(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[♪ pop music playing]
PERFECT CROWN
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS
WERE FILMED SAFELY
Tell me.
Who are you trying to save here? Yourself?
Or the Grand Prince?
Him.
[♪ tender music plays]
I can save myself.
You…
Please, Father.
[sighs]
Divorce him.
You bear the brunt of the allegations,
from ambitions for the throne
to the staged marriage,
and divorce him.
Father…
When he loses you, his weakness,
the opposition will
have nothing left to target.
Then the Grand Prince
will be able to fight back
without restraint.
[sniffles]
What if…
What if I want to save myself?
You said to choose between us.
That path, too,
leads to divorce.
Get out of that hellhole.
Avoid getting hurt any further.
[cries]
PERFECT CROWN
EPISODE 10
His Royal Highness is inside.
[breathes shakily]
-[door opens]
-[footsteps approaching]
Your Royal Highness.
[chuckles]
How's your father doing?
[chuckles] What's this? A gift?
[inhales sharply]
[sighs] Your Royal Highness.
Yes?
Let's get a divorce.
STYLE
::cue()
[sad music playing]
What are you talking about?
I think it's time…
we go our separate ways.
[sighs]
Father has fallen ill from all the stress.
The stocks are tanking,
and public sentiment is in the mud.
I heard there's a tax audit coming soon.
No wonder he's fallen ill.
I got married to become the successor.
But at this rate,
I won't even have a place to go back to.
I hear what you're saying, but…
It's not your fault.
We were both in the wrong.
But now,
I want to cut my losses.
That's why you want a divorce?
To cut your losses?
The quickest fix for stuff like this
is someone stepping up to take the fall.
Holding out isn't always the answer.
Did something happen while I was gone?
Did the Queen Mother--
Whatever the Queen Mother says to me
is none of your concern.
-Seong Huiju.
-I already told you.
[♪ sad music continues]
I'm not afraid of that
because I had no honor to begin with.
Royal dignity, propriety, or whatever.
I couldn't care less
about any of that crap.
Does it even exist?
-Seong Huiju!
-Everything I have
actually has substance.
They're things I've fought for…
and claimed with my own hands.
You said the duty
of a royal is to be loved.
You said that was power.
But you lost it all.
What could you possibly do for me now?
Don't do this.
Not you too…
You said you wouldn't hold me back.
You told me to just keep taking.
But I'm just losing everything right now.
And yet…
you wish to keep me bound to you?
[♪ music ends]
STYLE
::cue()
Your Royal Highness.
This is the Crown Prince's Quarters.
It is a hall without a master.
Your Royal Highness.
I wish to be alone.
Go back to Anhwadang Hall.
[♪ gentle music plays]
[exhales shakily]
[cries]
[I-AN] Brother.
Look after the Crown Princess.
You are all she has to rely on.
Must you make things hard for her?
[scoffs]
She relies on me?
[sighs] Brother.
I doubt she ever relied on me.
But even if she did,
what could I possibly do for her?
I am sure she is well aware.
Such is the nature
of my station.
[♪ gentle music plays]
And the same must be said
for the Crown Princess.
You are just being a coward.
Sure.
I hope you do not end up like me.
No.
I don't intend to.
Is this how it felt?
[♪ music continues]
STYLE
::cue()
Did you work through the night?
Yeah.
What is it?
What?
Say what you need to say.
Please let me get into the Council Hall.
We need their approval for a divorce.
I'd like to speak for myself.
Do so, then.
Aide Choi.
Are they really going to get divorced?
[stammers] Well, what can we do?
The party involved is intent on it.
And the Grand Prince doesn't get a say?
Well, His Royal Highness agreed to it…
No, but you know he doesn't mean it!
What sort of nonsense is that?
Something happened yesterday.
Is the chairman making her?
Your Royal Highness.
By chance, did the chairman--
I'm getting a divorce.
Pardon?
The whole world
refers to me as a stain on his reputation.
-Your Royal Highness, that's just--
-Stain or weakness…
They should be eliminated regardless.
If His Royal Highness refuses…
I need you to take my side.
The chairman is just a bit frustrated.
He didn't put her up to anything.
[chuckles]
Then why? Why, all of a sudden?
[phone buzzing]
Don't go anywhere. Wait here.
Yes, Your Royal Highness.
[sighs]
I understand, Your Royal Highness.
[♪ tense music playing]
[court staff]
Announcing Grand Prince I-AN.
STYLE
::cue()
LORD INPYEONG
Two days ago,
the Cabinet requested
that His Royal Highness
cease his official duties…
His Royal Highness and I…
will be getting a divorce.
[staff chattering]
-What is this now?
-All of a sudden?
Grand Princess!
Strip me of my rank.
I risked it all to gain royal status,
was a prime suspect
in the Junghwajeon Hall fire,
and collapsed after being poisoned.
[scoffs]
That was all me.
Grand Princess.
My point is, do not pin this
on the wrong person.
It appears you do not grasp
the gravity of this situation.
[Huiju] Prime Minister Min.
I was told the royal family
are not subject to investigation.
Without the king's approval,
it is difficult, but…
If I am stripped of my rank,
it should be easier to investigate me, no?
Approve our divorce
and investigate me.
[♪ dramatic music plays]
Seong Huiju.
Whether I'm the culprit behind the fire,
or I staged my own collapse.
Either way, I can prove that
the Grand Prince had no part in any of it.
So just do it.
And all this insolent talk of him
relinquishing the regency…
Enough of that.
[reporters chattering]
[Taeju] Why are there so many?
Babe, you got this, right?
A walk in the park. [sniffles]
Why couldn't she just do it herself?
Huiju is the Grand Princess now.
How could she?
Besides, the camera loves you more.
That's true. [clears throat]
Let's go.
[clears throat]
[reporter] There's CEO Seong Taeju!
[reporters clamoring]
-CEO Seong!
[shutters clicking]
-Please look over here.
-CEO Seong!
-Over here, sir!
-Over here, please!
-CEO Seong!
ADDRESSING THE MARRIAGE CONTRACT LEAK
[clears throat]
Oh, right.
Can you confirm that Castle Group
had no knowledge
of the marriage contract
between the Grand Prince and Princess?
There must be some sort of plan
behind the three-year-divorce promise…
Following the marriage, has the handover
of her management rights
-been properly finalized?
-Just a moment.
First, let's calm down.
There are allegations that she staged
her collapse. Is that true?
[shutters continue clicking]
-What?
-To hide the fact it was staged,
she was taken to Castle Hospital
and not Royal Seoul Hospital.
-Is that true?
-[scoffs]
They're even calling that a lie now?
[clears throat]
[reporters clamoring]
Ma'am.
Why would she take poison
when she had the world at her feet?
[reporters clamor]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
We just got started here.
AIDE CHOI HYEON
Regarding the contract,
Castle Group will be
watering things down on our end.
So I'd appreciate your patience.
It won't be a perfectly clean slate,
but it'll lose enough steam
to make it manageable.
Do you truly believe
it is that simple a matter?
I'm sure you all know how much money
was poured into our wedding.
And that more was made
than was ever spent.
It's surely not news to you.
Before all contributors start asking
for their money back,
shouldn't we at least deny the fact
that this marriage
was a sham?
[Taeju] For starters,
I assume all of you have seen
this marriage contract.
Does the Grand Prince benefit
at all from this contract?
Same goes for my sister.
It stipulates that she'll relinquish
all assets and real estate
acquired with her royal title
upon divorce.
Did you all miss that part?
-But this was for status--
-Hold on. Let me just say one thing.
Everyone here knows
the palace was dead set against them
when the scandal
about them dating first broke.
Even our family didn't believe
they would actually get married.
We told her to stop wasting time
and just focus on her work.
But what could we do?
They were madly in love.
[reporters chattering]
[reporter 1]
Well, if they're so madly in love,
why would they agree
to divorce within three years?
Right.
That is why I'm here today.
That clause.
It was per my request.
[reporter 2] Does that mean you were
involved in drawing up the contract?
[reporter 3]
Between the Crown and Castle Group?
They may be madly in love now,
but feelings fade.
I mean, she was even drugged
at her own wedding.
-It could make her want a divorce.
-[reporters murmur]
But since divorce is considered taboo
in the royal family,
I suggested they at least
draw up a contract.
But let's be real.
This wasn't even notarized by a lawyer.
I just went a little overboard
to protect my little sister.
I sincerely apologize
for the distress caused to the public.
That said…
you all keep spinning these stories
about pulling stunts and plotting treason.
All sorts of ridiculous nonsense…
I'll be saving all your articles as PDFs.
[reporters clamor]
[clears throat]
[♪ upbeat music plays]
You were so awesome, babe!
-Let's hurry home.
-Okay.
…all your articles as PDFs.
-You reviewed the draft for the PR team?
-Yes.
"Doting siblings," check.
"True love," check.
"Saving as PDFs," check.
All done.
Yes, I knew it!
They couldn't even look at each other
during the wedding rites
without blushing and getting all giddy.
How could that not be true love?
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
[sighs]
It should be over by now.
Without even consulting
with the Royal Secretariat?
We made it crystal clear that the Crown
has no ties to the contract.
We also clarified that the Grand Prince
stood to gain nothing from our marriage.
Any remaining controversy
will be mine to handle.
Once you cast me aside,
the Grand Prince can return…
to being the pride of the Crown.
[chuckles]
[officials murmuring]
Does His Royal Highness…
share this sentiment?
[♪ suspenseful music plays]
Grand Prince I-AN
shall receive His Majesty's command.
[♪ music ends]
[♪ gentle music plays]
Is this how it felt?
[♪ classical music plays]
Even so…
I refuse to live like you.
[♪ dramatic music plays]
Your Royal Highness.
His Majesty has just retired
to his bedchamber.
-Perhaps you can--
-Announce me.
Your Royal Highness.
I told you to announce me.
Your Majesty,
His Royal Highness has arrived.
[King] Show him in.
[♪ dramatic music continues]
Your Majesty.
I must ask you
to return my throne.
"Thus proclaims the King."
-"I, the King…"
-[King Seonjong] I, the King,
being overburdened in body and spirit,
can no longer govern the realm.
Thus, I intend to step down
from the throne.
The Crown Prince is far too young
and of a frail disposition
to assume such a heavy responsibility.
Fortunately, the heavens
have not forsaken us,
and have bestowed upon us the wise
STYLE
::cue()
and virtuous Grand Prince I-AN.
"I deem him fit
to serve the heavens
and the royal ancestors above,
and to care for the people
of the realm below."
As such, I, the King,
intend to abdicate the throne
in favor of my uncle,
Grand Prince I-AN.
"All officials of the Crown
and the Cabinet
shall receive and uphold
the new King with might."
[King Seonjong] And all the people shall
embrace the grand vision of the nation…
"THIRTY-SECOND KING"
…so that the realm may stand firm,
unshaken and everlasting.
What is the meaning of this?
A willful abdication?
I must see His Majesty.
Lord INPYEONG.
Do you dismiss the royal command
delivered by the Royal Secretariat?
[♪ triumphant music plays]
[♪ music ends]
Your Royal Highness.
Just hold on a second.
You said you were done losing.
That's why you want a divorce.
[sighs]
Your Royal Highness.
-I just…
-And yet,
how could you throw
everything on the line?
Did you truly believe…
I could not…
protect us?
It's not that…
You did not trust me.
Willful abdication?
The royal edict was announced in front
of the Cabinet and the royal family.
Why, all of a sudden?
Without so much as a warning.
-Tell me why!
-Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Fortunately, His Royal Highness refused…
That was just a formality!
He will refuse three times…
before he accepts.
[scoffs, cries]
That feeble bloodline has at last…
[grunts]
[straining]
[sighs]
Your Majesty.
Open the doors.
[court lady] His Majesty has locked them
from the inside.
[Yun] Your Majesty!
Open these doors!
-Your Majesty!
-[court lady] Please stop, Your Majesty.
[Yun] This is beyond the pale.
Your Majesty!
[Yun] Have you truly gone mad?
I would rather see you dead.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty,
please give His Majesty some time.
What is this time you speak of?
Your Majesty.
You must have known.
-Pardon?
-Court Lady Im.
[Im] Yes, Your Majesty.
[♪ tense music plays]
Break down these doors.
Your Majesty…
These are the King's Quarters.
How could I open them
without His Majesty's command?
Please rescind your command.
STYLE
::cue()
Start a fire if you must.
That should force him out.
[Jeongwoo] Your Majesty.
Let me escort you to your quarters.
Do not give me orders.
I have yet…
to give an order.
[♪ music ends]
We must allow no word of this to spread.
I will handle the Cabinet members.
You must see to it
that no word escapes the palace.
Am I the only one
horrified by this situation?
It is getting quite exhausting.
How much longer must I keep cleaning up
the royal family's mess?
This affects you as well.
If Grand Prince I-AN becomes king,
the Grand Princess will be bound
to the palace forever.
Is that what you desire?
That will not happen.
The Grand Prince will refuse three times
as a formality.
He refused once at the Council Hall today,
so he'll refuse two more times.
Before he does,
you must stop either
the Grand Prince or His Majesty.
Do whatever you must.
I shall put her poisoning case on hold.
But you agreed to handle that--
The handling of affairs you desire
shall be granted to you
once I get what I want.
Are you threatening me right now?
Yes.
Is there any reason I should not?
[sighs]
You did not trust me.
[footsteps approaching]
Why is it just you?
Where's the Grand Prince?
He left.
-He left? The palace?
-Yes.
What is he thinking,
leaving at a time like this?
He nearly died as just the Grand Prince.
Who knows what'll happen
after this royal abdication edict?
[dialing]
[phone ringing]
INCOMING CALL
JUNIOR ALUM
[line ringing]
[sighs]
Stop it.
How will you ever divorce him
at this rate?
Aide Choi and I will find
the Grand Prince.
You stay here.
Can't have you missing each other.
[sighs]
[♪ gentle music plays]
If I say I wish to ascend the throne,
all would condemn me and hurl insults.
But I believe
you would understand me.
[♪ contemplative music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
"Leading the way."
How do you do it?
You just need to walk by my side.
I'll teach you.
[♪ contemplative music continues]
[exhales deeply]
[♪ pop music playing, WOODZ "Everglow"]
Just let me be for a second.
I'll come back down
once my anger subsides a bit.
[I-AN clears throat]
[I-AN] I do like you.
And it's my first time.
You should just accept it all.
Whether it be money, honor,
or my heart…
[sniffles]
[sobs]
[sobbing]
[♪ music ends]
Aide Do, here's what you asked for.
-Let's go.
-Where?
His Royal Highness left the palace
and won't take the Grand Princess's calls.
What? What about the Royal Guard?
No need to call them. I know where he is.
[I-AN] After the royal abdication edict
is delivered,
His Majesty will lock himself
in his quarters.
I will leave and head to
my private residence.
I must be gone
so the Grand Princess
does not get embroiled in the chaos.
[sighs]
I understand, Your Royal Highness.
Wow, so you knew all along?
Then why didn't you loop me in?
You didn't loop me in, either.
About the Grand Princess's plan.
Right. That's true.
Wait, so where are we going?
-To get a drink.
-[Hyeon] What?
[breathing heavily]
[Hyejeong] Everything's a mess anyway.
Might as well have a drink
since it's not allowed in the palace.
Well, th-that's true…
[breathes deeply]
[Hyejeong sighs]
This is it.
This is what I like.
That's random.
You asked what I liked.
This is what I like.
With the Hangang River here.
[sighs]
[♪ gentle music playing]
What do you think?
[smacks lips]
Well, it's…
I-I like it.
[chuckles softly]
What exactly?
The river?
The alcohol?
Or me?
[♪ hopeful music playing]
STYLE
::cue()
[inhales sharply]
[chuckles softly]
[chuckles]
[exhales sharply]
[breathes deeply]
[Hyeon mutters]
-I like it all. I like the whole lot.
-[chuckles]
[crickets chirping]
[Huiju] Where are you?
Did you have dinner?
I get that you're angry and all,
but how could you just leave like this?
[sighs]
You're somewhere safe, right? [sighs]
I swear, I will track your location.
Is Aide Do even looking for him or what?
Your Royal Highness.
Yes?
[chuckles]
There was this one day
when His Royal Highness
climbed over this wall.
He seemed exceptionally happy that day.
I wondered if he'd hidden
a sweet pot of honey here.
It wasn't until the next day
that I found out
that a maiden was responsible.
[chuckles]
[Lady Choi] And so,
I have faith in the both of you.
You are both desperate
to protect one another, are you not?
[Lady Choi inhales deeply]
The palace gates will be shut soon.
[gasps]
Then can I just…
[♪ upbeat pop music playing]
[breathes heavily]
Oh.
But what if someone asks for me?
Do not worry.
[♪ upbeat pop music continues]
[pants]
[Huiju] I'm sick.
PRINCE
[exhales deeply]
[phone buzzes]
[engine revving]
[footsteps approaching]
[panting]
[♪ music ends]
[pants]
I thought you were sick.
[breathes heavily]
I just wanted to be with you.
I told you I'd be back tomorrow.
[breathing shakily]
Are you okay?
I like you.
[♪ gentle music playing]
Stick to one thing.
I'm getting confused.
No, you're not.
You know I like you.
STYLE
::cue()
And that I only asked
for a divorce to protect you.
That's why you're mad.
[♪ pop music playing, WOODZ "Everglow"]
You don't want this?
I do.
[objects clatter]
[I-AN chuckles]
[kissing]
[♪ song ends]
[birds chirping]
Your Royal Highness?
You're awake.
What's going on?
[sighs]
I got a call from the palace.
What's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
[sighs]
I was just a little scared.
[I-AN sighs]
Stay here for the time being.
By myself? Why?
The second edict will be delivered soon.
And I will
refuse it once more.
Hold on a second.
One step at a time.
Walk me through step by step
so I can understand.
With a royal abdication edict,
it's customary to refuse three times.
And then?
I have to accept it.
But you wanted to protect His Majesty.
I wanted to protect my nephew.
Not the king.
-Whoosh.
-[chuckles]
[I-AN] Whoosh.
[Yun] You intend for Grand Prince I-AN
to ascend the throne?
Have you truly gone mad?
[breathes shakily]
[♪ tense music playing]
[sighs]
STYLE
::cue()
What is this?
His Majesty had a garment made for you.
[gasps, breathes shakily]
[♪ tense music intensifies]
[sighs]
It appears my brother…
seeks to abdicate.
But what about the Crown Prince?
[I-AN] I hated him for it.
He turned a blind eye
when I longed for it so desperately.
It felt like he was thrusting the burden
when it was far too late.
[Hyeon] Your Royal Highness!
[footsteps running]
[panting]
Something terrible has happened.
[I-AN] But…
I was the one too late.
[♪ music ends]
[♪ mournful music playing]
[I-AN] So I wanted to protect my nephew,
no matter what.
In my brother's place.
Where is the Crown Prince?
[guard] Pardon?
Where is my nephew…
the heir to the throne?
[♪ mournful music continues]
[I-AN] When the Queen Mother
turned a blind eye
to my brother's dying wish…
[breathes shakily]
Even when my nephew told me he was scared…
[breathing shakily]
I hesitated.
If I become king,
I feel like I could protect everyone.
But then again…
I fear it's just my own greed.
You can be greedy.
Let's see this through.
I will be by your side.
[♪ mournful music intensifies]
[protestor on megaphone]
Remove Grand Prince I-AN as regent!
-Remove him!
[protestor]
Strip Seong Huiju of her rank immediately!
-Immediately!
[protestor] Grand Prince I-AN and
CEO Seong Huiju must apologize!
[protestors chanting]
Apologize! Apologize!
Your Royal Highness.
[protestors continue chanting
indistinctly]
The Queen Mother is asking for you.
All right.
[sighs]
[door closes]
Tell them you cannot accept.
[sighs]
[scoffs]
Surely you do not intend to accept.
His Majesty has
only eight years of life to his name.
He is incapable
of forming thoughts or intentions!
That is it!
That is exactly the issue.
He has no will
or mind of his own, yet you have him
sit up there as a puppet
tossing him about as you please!
STYLE
::cue()
That is precisely the issue.
Is that what you told His Majesty?
You are the one who made
the king into a puppet!
Yes.
I let that happen.
Whether beside or behind him,
he was easily pushed around.
[♪ contemplative music playing]
So now…
I must stand in front of him.
I-AN!
[breathing shakily]
[sighs]
Queen Mother.
You should be thankful
he stepped down on his own.
In consideration of his filial devotion,
I will not ask you…
to pay for your sins.
Why?
Why insist on becoming king only now?
[Yun crying]
[♪ contemplative piano music playing]
I have made my sacrifices.
So you must do the same.
[crying] That is only fair!
[sobbing]
I gave up on my dreams.
You must become the Crown Princess.
[Yun] My future.
[students chattering]
[I-AN] Yun Irang!
[♪ gentle music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[Yun crying] And even my heart.
So why?
[breathes shakily]
Why won't you give anything up? [cries]
[sobbing]
[I-AN] Court Lady Im, are you there?
[exhales shakily]
Her Majesty appears weary
in mind and body.
For the next three days,
permit no one to enter her quarters.
[Lady Im] Yes, Your Royal Highness.
[breathes shakily]
-[exhales sharply]
-[Lady Im] Your Majesty…
[sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
[rain pattering]
[Lord INPYEONG on phone]
What on earth are you doing?
If His Majesty refused to open the doors,
you should've torn them down!
[sighs] Never mind.
I will head there now--
[Yun] It will all be in vain.
For the next three days,
no one will be permitted
to enter my quarters.
And why is that?
If the Grand Prince accepts
the abdication,
he will destroy us.
[sighs]
He has stated
he will not hold me accountable.
[Lord INPYEONG] Do you really believe…
[breathing heavily]
Ignoring the late King's dying wish
isn't our only crime.
Even if Prime Minister Min
is covering for us now,
-if he becomes king--
-That is enough!
Do you intend to surrender
all privileges held by the royal family?
Father!
I will take over from here.
STYLE
::cue()
What are you plotting now?
It will be too late after his ascension.
What does that mean?
[Lord INPYEONG] Your Majesty,
you just need to protect your quarters.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Father?
-[call ends]
-[gasps]
[staff member]
Lord INPYEONG, you have a guest.
[♪ suspenseful music intensifies]
[♪ music fades]
[rain pattering]
[♪ gentle music playing]
-Wow. Is this what he's wearing today?
-Yes.
The last edict will be
personally delivered by His Majesty.
[sucks teeth] But he didn't wear this
to His Majesty's Royal Birthday Banquet?
[gasps] Thank you for bringing that up.
-I went through hell that day--
-[clears throat]
-[chuckles softly]
-[Lady Choi sobbing]
Oh…
His Majesty, the late King,
would have been delighted to see this.
[chuckles, sniffles]
[chuckles softly]
I'm delighted too.
[chuckles]
[Hyejeong] Your Royal Highness.
The Royal Secretariat has notified
the Office of Royal Relatives
and the Prime Minister.
Goodness, they'll all be racing
to the palace now.
[Hyejeong] Before that, we have
some documents from the Secretariat
and Rites for your review.
Are you ready to go?
[♪ hopeful music playing]
I'll be waiting here.
[chuckles softly]
Okay.
[Lady Im] Your Majesty,
His Majesty has arrived.
[door opens]
What brings you here?
Mother.
If you do not intend to rescind it,
you should turn back.
I…
Your father fought to protect that throne!
[His Majesty cries]
Do you have any idea
what he went through to safeguard it?
Do you know what I had to do
to ensure it was passed down to you--
I know!
[sobbing] The day Father passed away…
I heard everything.
-[sobs]
-[gasps]
[♪ mournful music playing]
[gasps]
[His Majesty crying]
How…
[His Majesty crying] I do not want to!
[Yun] Crown Prince!
I do not want to!
[Yun sniffles]
It was your father's dying wish.
[crying]
The only one I can rely on now
is you, Crown Prince…
No. Your Majesty.
[His Majesty crying]
Do not disappoint me.
[breathing shakily]
STYLE
::cue()
Mother!
[sobs]
Mother, please forgive me
for disappointing you.
[Yun breathes shakily]
[His Majesty sobbing]
[both crying]
[♪ mournful music continues]
[both sobbing]
[♪ music fades]
Sir.
It's time to head to the Council Hall now.
There's still plenty of time.
[secretary] Yes, sir.
[sighs]
[♪ contemplative music playing]
[birds chirping]
I will take over from here.
[sighs]
[Jeongwoo] You must stop either
the Grand Prince or His Majesty.
Do whatever you must.
[I-AN] I will not ask you
to pay for your sins.
[sighs]
I-AN
[line ringing]
[phone buzzes]
Your Royal Highness,
it is the Queen Mother.
[continues buzzing]
[Jeongwoo] I'd like a brief audience
in the Council Hall.
Do we have time
before we're due at the Throne Hall?
Well…
Yes, we have about 30 minutes.
Right.
[sighs]
[♪ tense music playing]
Court Lady Im.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I need the girl I hid…
brought to the palace.
PROTOCOL FOR THE ACCESSION
OF THE 34TH KING
[sighing]
[sucks teeth] Be honest with me.
About what?
If I become…
If I become the Queen,
people wouldn't like it, right?
Come on now. Your Royal Highness?
Who would ever?
My goodness. Who would dare?
If I ever find them…
Hyejeong would've been
brutally honest with me.
Yes. Well, they won't be too thrilled.
-[chuckles]
-[groans]
Right, exactly!
If I had known about this,
I wouldn't have stepped up.
I was planning
to just take the fall for it
and bounce out of here
without looking back.
No need to get worked up.
Not everyone is a fan
of the Grand Prince, either. [chuckles]
I only have haters.
Oh, I see.
You can do it!
[phone buzzes]
PAIN IN MY ASS
[line ringing]
[Huiju] Yes?
Hey, you said you'd call.
I've been waiting forever, you know.
Should I move to the next step?
Father in the hospital?
No. Don't. Just stop that for now.
Stop? Why? Are they
calling off the company audit?
No, that's not it.
[sighs] Where are you now? Father's place?
-Yeah.
-[Huiju] Stay there. I'll be right over.
-At least tell me what's going…
-[call ends]
Damn brat.
Why? What did Huiju say?
-She's coming here.
-What?
STYLE
::cue()
[sucks teeth]
[♪ tense music playing]
[explosion in distance]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Grand Princess.
You must flee.
[gasps]
Isn't that… the Council Hall?
[explosion]
[breathes shakily]
No…
[breathes shakily] No!
Your Highness!
[clamoring]
[panting, exclaims]
[breathing heavily]
Aide Do.
What…
What are you doing here?
[breathes shakily]
Tell me.
[breathing shakily, whimpers]
Do Hyejeong!
The Council Hall…
His Royal Highness.
He's in the Council Hall.
[breathing shakily]
[♪ dramatic music intensifies]
Your Royal Highness.
[breathes shakily]
[♪ music fades]
PERFECT CROWN
[| contemplative music playing,
Byeon Wooseok, "Parallel"]
[Hyejeong] His Royal Highness.
He's in the Council Hall.
[Huiju] Your Royal Highness!
Your Royal Highness! [exclaims]
[secretary] There's a rumor circulating
that the Grand Prince has passed away.
What do you mean, regency?
[Jeongwoo] Since the Grand Prince
remains unconscious,
it would only be fitting
for Your Majesty to step forward.
[Hyejeong] The Grand Prince is awake!
[I-AN] I hear rumors of my passing
are spreading outside these walls.
[Huiju] How could one measly royal guard
blow up the Council Hall by himself?
Since the Grand Prince
has regained consciousness,
it's time we tied up some loose ends.
[Huiju] How much do you trust Jeongwoo?
Is there any place safe for you?
Translated by Justin S. Kim
[♪ pop music playing]
PERFECT CROWN